Courtney!
柯特妮!
I had this sensation of someone taking my hand, guiding me...
有一种感觉有人牵着我的手 指引我...
I looked up and I saw this light.
我抬起头看见这道光
The giant wall of light. Brighter...
一面巨大的光墙 非常的明亮...
All of a sudden, I was in a different place.
突然间 我在一个不同的地方
Pure energy.
纯粹的能量
I fail to find words that can describe what I experienced.
我无法用文字表达我经历过的事
At that point, I had that out-of-body experience.
在当时 我有着灵魂出窍的经验
I remember a feeling of being sucked backwards,
我记得一种被吸回的感觉
like being pulled through water.
就像是被拉进水里一样
I wasn't having thoughts of my own.
我没有自己的想法
Answers, messages coming through me.
答案和讯息藉由我传递
Colors were so vivid. Colors I've never seen before.
颜色非常的鲜明 是我从来没见过的
Then I was pushed right back into my body.
然后我被推回我自己的身体
I could actually see my body from above,
我可以从上方看见我自己的身体
like it was lifeless.
仿佛没有生命似的
And I was floating up...
当我漂浮起来...
Everything I thought was important was
我所认为每件重要的事情
dwarfed by this sense of love.
都与这种爱的感觉无法媲美
And I could feel this pull,
我可以感受这种拉力
a force trying to drag me down this black tunnel.
一股想要将我拉进黑色隧道的力量
Where is it taking me?
它想带我去哪里?
I don't know what's going on.
我不知道怎么了
I think I'm going crazy.
我想我要疯了
I'm seeing things.
我看见某些事情
Something I did.
某些我做过的事情
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
(九年后)
Hello, Lauren.
哈啰 罗伦
How are you feeling?
你感觉还好吗?
You had a seizure tonight.
你今晚癫痫发作了
You're at Trinity Emmanuel Medical Center.
你在三一伊曼纽尔医学中心
Lauren,
罗伦
do you know that your heart stopped?
你知道你的心跳停止了吗?
You were gone for several minutes,
你死了几分钟
but the trauma team brought you back.
但是创伤团队把你带了回来
Do you remember any of that?
你还记得吗?
If you felt anything, if you saw anything?
你有感觉到什么 看到什么吗?
Did you lose someone, sweetheart?
甜心 你有失去某人吗?
She's in here.
她在这里
We're taking you to Imaging. You'll be okay.
我们要带你去拍影像 会没事的
One for transfer in five.
五分钟后有一位病人转院
Ready? One, two, three.
预备? 一 二 三
Transfer from Holy Cross.
从圣十字架医院转过来的
38-year-old construction worker, fell off a beam.
一位三十八岁的建筑工人 从梁柱上掉下来
Persistent coma. GCS 6.
持续昏迷 昏迷指数六
I'll page the resident.
我来呼叫驻院医师
Already done. I got this.
我已经叫了
- Which one of you is in charge here? - It's my intake.
- 你们这里是谁负责? - 这是我的病人
Actually, I'm the one on duty.
事实上 是我在值班
I got it. I got it. Thank you.
我来 谢谢
Standard procedure for a GCS 6 admit
昏迷指数六的标准程序
calls for two large-bore IVs and diazepam on standby.
需要做两次大口径静脉注射 准备地西泮
Seizure meds won't do any good.
癫痫药物不会有帮助
Whatever is wrong is in his spinal column, not his brain.
是他的脊柱出了问题 不是他的脑部
And what medical protocol are you citing?
你说出了哪种治疗计划?
The protocol of actually living in the real world,
真实存在世界上的治疗计划
where guys with crappy HMOs go undiagnosed for spinal injuries.
一间很烂的健康维护机构的人 没有诊断为脊柱损伤
Actually, he's on seizure meds,
事实上 他在服用癫痫药物
which is the medical protocol of reading his chart.
那是读了他的诊断表后所做出的治疗计划
Shit. No, no, no.
该死的 不
- Shit. - What is it?
- 该死 - 怎么了?
Respiratory failure.
呼吸道衰竭
He might be hemorrhaging.
他可能有出血
Page Neurosurgery, call a code, and get CT on standby.
呼叫神经外科 用代码 准备断层扫描
Students, clear the room.
学生们 将房间清场
(来世及其奥秘)
(几十年研究只有产生少数新验证数据 以及许多问题)
Hey. What is it? What's wrong?
嘿 怎么了?
Did you know that there's 12 pairs of nerves
你知道在脑颅区就有
just within the cranial area?
十二对神经吗?
The oculomotor, the trochlear, the glossopharyngeal, and...
动眼神经 滑车神经 舌咽神经 还有...
Nine others whose names I cannot remember.
其他九条我不记得名字的神经
I cannot absorb any more terminology.
我无法再吸收更多的术语
I have, like, a rash on my arm. I can't sleep.
我手上起了疹子 我睡不着
You know, my mother invested
我知道 我母亲投入了
her entire life savings into my education.
她一生的积蓄在我的教育上
Come on.
来吧
Come on, that's enough suffering for one night.
来吧 今晚折腾够了
Let's get out of here. Yeah?
我们走吧 好吗?
It's cold.
好冷
We used to be friends, right?
我们以前是朋友 对吗?
- What is... - Like, our first year,
- 什么... - 第一年的时候
when we would sit together at lecture. Remember?
当我们在课堂中坐在一起的时候 记得吗?
And we'd, like, go running and get coffee.
我们一起跑步 买咖啡
Hang out. Do stuff.
一起闲聊 一起做事
We're still friends, though.
我们仍然还是朋友
No, we don't talk.
不 我们不讲话了
We just work and compete.
我们之间只有工作和竞争
Who's the fastest to make a diagnosis of Bell's palsy?
谁可以最快诊断出贝尔的麻痹原因?
Quick, what's the seven side effects of Ativan?
快点 萝拉西泮的七个副作用是什么?
You know, just last week, a second-year committed suicide.
你知道 上周 一位二年级学生自杀
God, Court, you're gonna be such a good doctor.
天啊 柯特 你会成为一个非常棒的医生
Medicine just, like, comes easy to you.
医药对你来说很简单
You know, I think there's a way that we could spend more time together.
你知道 我有办法 让我们多一点时间相处
- What do you mean? - Well, I'm just wondering
- 什么意思? - 呃 我只是在想
if you'd help me on this little, like,
如果你在这件事情上帮我
extracurricular project I've been working on.
我一直在研究的课外项目
We have neuro shelf exams in, like, 10 days.
十天后我们有一个神经学验收考试
I don't really feel like I'm gonna make it.
我感觉我做不到
Oh, Once One Takes The Anatomy Final, Very Good Vacations Are Heavenly.
一旦有人赢得解剖学期末考 就可以得到一个很棒的假期
- What? - It's a mnemonic phrase.
- 什么? - 那是助记词
You use it to remember the 12 cranial nerves.
你用它来记住十二条颅神经
- Yeah. - Thank you.
- 好 - 谢谢你
You're welcome.
不客气
But, yeah, I really would love your help.
但是 我真的需要你的帮忙
Maybe.
或许吧
Hey.
嘿
What's in those?
那里面是什么?
First one's Mountain Dew laced with Adderall.
第一个是加了聪明药的汽水
Other's a chaser of espressos.
另外一个是浓缩咖啡
- Together, it's a liquid heart attack. - Hey, Jamie.
- 在一起 是液体的心脏病 - 嘿 杰米
Jesus.
天啊
Hey.
嘿
"Hey, Jamie." Where were you last night?
"嘿 杰米" 你昨晚去哪里了?
Your eyes are still dilated.
你的瞳孔还在扩张
25-year-old female, admitted last night.
二十五岁的女性 昨晚来住院
Complaining of numbness on left side, nausea, vomiting.
抱怨左半边麻痹 有恶心和呕吐的情形
Anything of note from the physical exam?
身体检查有什么要注意的吗?
Sees the color red differently between left and right eye, and oral ulcers.
左右眼看红色不相同 还有口腔溃疡
Sophia, what test should we run?
苏菲亚 我们应该做什么测试?
A lumbar puncture, then MRI of the brain.
腰椎穿刺 脑部核磁共振
Fine, but reverse the order. Images first, then procedure.
好 但是顺序相反 先去成像然后再进行程序
Preliminary diagnosis, Brad.
布莱德 初步诊断
- Pituitary cyst? - No.
- 垂体囊肿? - 不是
Jamie.
杰米
Jackie.
杰奇
- Stroke? - My God.
- 中风吗? - 我的天
You need to do better than this.
你必须再加把劲
All of you.
你们所有的人都是
What do you think the largest age demographic is in our society today?
你认为现今社会最多人口的年龄阶层是什么?
You.
就是你们
Young adults in their 20s, which means
二十多岁的年轻成人 那表示
that there are at least 1,000 people waiting
至少有一千人在等待着
to take your spot.
要拿走你的位置
And we are not in the business of training country club doctors,
我们不是在做 训练乡村俱乐部医生的生意
nor do we waste our time on students who think
也不是在那些他们认为可以做最少的
that they can skate by doing the least work necessary.
必要工作的学生身上浪费时间
We are here to educate students who push themselves,
我们是来这里教育学生要督促自己
those who are capable of making new discoveries
那些能够做出新发现的
and actually move the dial on human knowledge.
实际上对人类知识产生影响
And for those of you who think that's too much,
对那些认为事情太多的人
then you should leave.
你们现在可以离开了
And by that, I mean now.
我是说现在
Marlo, if I were to tell you
玛洛 如果我告诉你
that the patient's family background was Mediterranean,
病人的家族来自地中海地区
i.e., Greek or Turkish, what would the diagnosis be?
例如说希腊和土耳其 诊断会是什么?
I don't think you'll find it in your notebook.
我想你在笔记中是找不到的
It's Behcet's disease.
是白塞病
Thank you, Ray.
瑞 谢谢你
Moving on.
请继续
Why are you working this event?
你为什么要在这里工作?
You're a trust-fund kid. You sleep on a sailboat.
你是信托基金养大的孩子 你睡在帆船上
Yeah, but there's this really hot caterer
对 但是有一位我非常想认识的
I've been trying to meet.
很辣的服务员
Look at all these stodgy old docs with their white wine
看看这些拿着白酒 聊着他们高尔夫球赛
and their golf games.
平庸的老医生
I don't think it's such a bad life.
我不觉得他们过得很糟
I don't know about you,
我不知道你怎么想的
but I'm certainly not gonna spend the next 40 years doing prostate exams.
但我绝对不想花未来四十年的时间 做前列腺检查
No one pays their dues anymore.
没人尽到自己的责任
Our generation, it's all about entrepreneurship.
我们这一代都和企业家精神有关
Yeah, so what are you gonna do?
对 所以你想做什么?
I'm going to LA.
我要去洛杉矶
Look at this face.
看看这张脸
I'm gonna be the Anderson Cooper of celebrity medicine.
我要当名人医学的安德森古柏
Okay.
好
"Hi, Mom. It's my afternoon check-in."
"嗨 妈 我下午的报到时间到了"
That's funny. Cool. Okay.
很有趣 酷 好
You know there's nothing I can do about her right now.
你知道我现在对她无能为力
Did she really move here just to keep tabs on you?
她真的是为了要追踪你 才搬到这里的吗?
Hey, come on, look.
嘿 快看
- My station is full. - Okay.
- 我的工作站满了 - 好
You're so behind.
你进度落后太多
Okay, sir, got to give you a testicular exam.
好 先生 要帮你做睾丸检查
- Should just take a minute. - What? No.
- 一下子就好了 - 什么? 不
- Excuse the reach. - Wait a minute.
- 抱歉我要摸了 - 等一下
I don't enjoy it either.
我也不是很喜欢
Just close your eyes and pretend I'm the candy-stripe girl.
眼睛闭起来假装我是糖果条纹女孩
What? Get, get the hell off of me!
什么? 放开我!
Hold on.
等一下
- Candy-stripe girl. - Get...
- 糖果条纹女孩 - 去...
- No, wait a minute. - Stop! What are you doing?
- 不 等一下 - 停下来! 你在做什么?
He doesn't need a testicular exam.
他不需要做睾丸检查
He doesn't?
他不用做吗?
Come near me again, and I'm killing you.
你再靠近我 我就杀了你
You know, I think I got mixed up.
你懂的 我被搞混了
It says here the resident wanted
这里说着驻院医生需要
a neural test for that guy, not a testicular exam.
帮那家伙做脑部检查 不是睾丸检查
I can't imagine how I passed the wrong information to you.
我不敢相信我讯息传递错误
Very funny.
很有趣
Ray can be a real dick sometimes. You guys notice that?
瑞有时真的有病 你们注意到了吗?
I think he's intriguing.
我认为他是个奇妙的人
Let's go, people. No lunch break today.
走吧 各位 今天没有午餐时间
Every bed in the unit is full, and we got referrals waiting in the ER.
医院里每张床都满了 急诊室里有等着转诊的人
Get moving on afternoon rounds.
下午的回合开始
Excuse me.
抱歉
Do you have plans tonight?
你今晚有计划吗?
First-years are having a wingding.
一年级学生要办狂欢会
Dorm punch and a deejay, but I'm not above it.
宿舍水果酒派对和DJ 但我不会参加
I can't wait for the anesthesia rotation.
我等不及要做麻醉轮训
Those guys have access to the best drugs.
那些家伙可以拿到最好的药
Looking for this?
你在找这个吗?
Hell yeah.
没错
I found it on my nightstand.
我在我床头柜发现的
See you later.
待会见
These second-years have no tact,
这些二年级学生一点分寸也没有
coming up to me like that in front of my colleague.
在我的同事面前这样对我说话
Yeah, we're colleagues, aren't we?
对 我们是同事不是吗?
I mean, we have fun together.
我们在一起很有趣
Yeah, kinda.
对 算是吧
Do you want to have fun with me later?
你等一下要跟我一起玩吗?
Courtney Holmes, I am mildly surprised
柯特妮荷姆斯 我有点惊讶
to be having this conversation with you.
会跟你有这种对话
But offer accepted.
但是我接受你的条件
Midnight, basement, sub level C.
半夜 地下室C层
You want to meet me in the basement?
你要跟我在地下室见面吗?
Sublevel C, underneath the old building.
地下C层 在旧建筑的下面
And take the service elevator,
搭送货电梯
'cause it doesn't have surveillance cameras.
因为没有监视器
Yeah. Good idea.
对 好主意
No.
不
Jesus!
天啊!
You're late.
你迟到了
What are we doing down here?
我们在这里做什么?
Come on, we don't have much time.
来吧 我们没时间了
Okay, Courtney, what's going on?
好 柯特妮 怎么了?
It's past midnight. I should be studying.
过了半夜 我应该要读书了
We're almost there, okay?
我们快到了 好吗?
(禁区 仅限授权人员出入)
What is all of this?
这些是什么?
They put this in five years ago.
它们五年前出现的
In case of a natural disaster, loss of power.
以防出现天灾 停电时用
It's a fully functioning hospital, and it never gets used.
这是一间功能完全的医院 从未被使用过
Court, what exactly are you up to?
柯特 你到底想做什么?
Two of you.
你们两个
Jamie, what are you doing here?
杰米 你在这里做什么?
She didn't tell me about you either, okay?
她也没告诉我你的事 好吗?
But, I'm open to a three-way.
但是 我对三P是很开放的
Shut up.
闭嘴
What?
什么?
I like it.
我喜欢
Scanners, cameras, our choice of beds.
扫瞄器 摄影机 床由我们选择
- We can be as loud as we want. - Courtney, what's going on?
- 我们可以尽可能地大声 - 柯特妮 怎么了?
I asked for his help, too. He probably misinterpreted.
我也请他帮忙 他可能误会了
You mean we're not getting it on?
你是说我们不会做吗?
Wait, what are you talking about?
等一下 你在说什么?
I've been searching for the region of the brain
我一直在寻找大脑中
that is responsible for near-death experiences.
负责濒死经验的区域
And these are postmortem scans
这些是在这间医院去世的
of patients that have died in this hospital.
病人的死后扫描
Is there any circumstance under which
你在怎样的情况之下
- you'd have sex with me? - God, stop.
- 有可能跟我性交? - 天啊 停止
Look, if the brain is just another organ,
听着 如果大脑只是另一个器官
why doesn't it just go dark and shut off
它为什么不会在死亡时
at the moment of death?
变暗并且关闭功能?
You know, why the floating?
你知道 为何会出窍?
Why the white light?
为何会有白光?
Why the sense of well-being?
为何会有幸福的感觉?
I mean, what is that experience?
我是说 那种经验是什么?
Is it chemical, or is it something else?
是化学反应 还是其他的东西?
Can we map that process the way we map a seizure?
我们可以像癫痫发作时一样的 刻划出这种程序吗?
What if we could actually document what happens to us after we die?
如果我们可以用文件纪录 我们死后发生的事呢?
What do you mean?
你是什么意思?
Nothing happens. We're dead.
没事发生 我们就是死了
What if we could prove otherwise?
如果我们可以反向证明呢?
Can you imagine the residency offers you would get?
你可以想像你会收到多好的 驻院医师条件吗?
And forget about Dr. Oz.
别管《奥兹医生秀》了
I mean, you would be the world's first specialist in the afterlife.
我是说 你会成为世界上第一位 死后专科医生
Okay, you got my attention.
好 我有点心动了
Come on. This isn't science.
来吧 这不是科学
This is pseudoscience.
这是伪科学
Well, maybe. Maybe not.
或许是 或许不是
But the only way to find out is to see for ourselves.
但去发现唯一的方法 是由我们亲眼所见
So I would like you both to stop my heart.
所以我希望你们两个 可以停止我的心跳
Look, I'll be in the imaging scanner.
听着 我会在成像扫描器中
It will take real-time pictures of my brain's hemodynamic activity.
我会照下我脑部 血液动力活动的即时照片
You give it one minute, and then you bring me back.
你拍一分钟 然后再让我醒来
Wait, you're serious?
等一下 你是认真的吗?
- Stop your heart? - This is propofol.
- 让你的心跳停止? - 这是异丙酚
Fifty milligrams will knock me out.
五十毫克就会让我晕过去
I'll be wrapped in a cooling blanket,
我会被包在冷冻毯里
bringing my core body temperature down to 86 degrees.
我的核心体温降到三十度
And once that happens,
当它发生时
you administer a defibrillator shock to stop my heart.
你控制除颤器电击 将我的心跳停止
Wait a sec.
等一下
Look, I've signed a release. It's in my bag.
听着 我签了同意书 在我的袋子里
It absolves you both of any responsibility.
那会免除你们两个任何的责任
Courtney, think about what you're saying right now.
柯特妮 想想看你现在说的话
Hey. Look, if she's insane enough to try it, who are we to stop her?
嘿 听着 如果她够疯狂想要尝试 又有谁可以阻止她呢?
Look, I'm young, okay? I'm in excellent health.
听着 我很年轻 好吗? 我也很健康
You're both trained in emergency medicine.
你们两个都有受过紧急医疗训练
So reviving me should be very straightforward.
所以让我复活应该不是件难事
Look, it's 12:18 now.
听着 现在是十二点十八分
I've checked the schedules for security down here
我查过这里的警卫和
and cleaning crews.
清扫人员的时间
We have about 45 minutes, so we should probably get going.
我们大概有四十五分钟 所以我们最好快点开始
What? This is crazy. No, count me out of this.
什么? 这真是疯狂 不 别把我算在内
I am not helping you kill yourself.
我不要帮你自杀
Well, then you can stand by the door and make sure nobody comes in.
那你可以站在门边 确定没有人会进来
Okay, remember, there's a magnet in the scanner,
好 记得 扫描器里有块磁铁
so no keys or metal in the room.
所以房间里不可以有钥匙或是金属
Look, we've got it.
听着 我们知道了
Wait, Jamie, what if you can't bring her back?
等一下 杰米 如果她回不来怎么办?
Then we burn her body, work out our alibi,
那我们就烧了她的尸体 编造不在场证明
and pretend like nothing happened.
假装一切都没发生过
And make sure that the scanner's recording,
确定那台扫描器有在纪录
because if not, then this whole exercise is pointless.
因为如果没有的话 这整个实验就是无效的
We're good to go.
我们准备好了
Repeat back to me the resuscitation procedure.
重复一次复活程序给我听
As soon as you're dead, I'll run the scanner.
你死的那一瞬间 我会启动扫描器
At 60 seconds, I'll start pulling you out
六十秒的时候 我会开始救你回来
by switching to the heating blanket.
打开加热毯
When your core temp's back up to 93 degrees, I'll start CPR.
当你的核心温度到达三十三度时 我就开始实行心肺复苏术
Crash cart is standing by with the epi and the defib.
有着肾上腺素和除颤器的急救车准备好了
Hello? Brain damage. You'll get brain damage.
哈啰? 你会有脑损伤
Not if you resuscitate me in time.
只要你们及时让我复苏就不会有
Brain cells can survive without oxygen for at least four minutes.
没有氧气的脑细胞可以至少存活四分钟
Okay.
好
Now is the point where you say it's all a joke.
有没有可能你刚才说的都是笑话
Okay, put the blanket on me.
好 帮我盖毯子
Jamie, look at her. Come on, she's terrified.
杰米 看着她 拜托 她吓死了
It's just my body's natural survival instincts.
那只是我身体的自然求生本能
I anticipated this. I'm trying to block it out.
我预料到了会这样 我试着将它排除在外
Okay.
好
And now I kill you.
我现在要杀了你
Come on, you'll both get expelled. You'll go to prison.
来吧 你们两个会被开除然后去坐牢
Only if you blab about it.
只要你不说就没事
Okay. We're really doing this.
好 真的要开始了
See you later.
待会见
She's out.
她无意识了
Body temp's dropping.
体温下降
Okay, look, Jamie, we can stop right here, okay?
好 听着 杰米 我们可以停了 好吗?
She sleeps it off, wakes up,
她就睡了一觉 醒来
and we just pretend that we followed through with it.
我们就假装我们做过了
If you can't handle this, then look away.
如果你无法处理 站到一边去
Fine. Yeah, Jamie, I'll just leave!
好 杰米 我离开就是了!
- Charging 200. - Come on! This is wrong!
- 充电两百焦耳 - 拜托! 这是错误的!
- Weren't you leaving? - You're murdering somebody!
- 你不是要走了吗? - 你在谋杀某人!
Yeah, I probably should've stayed in tonight.
对 我或许今晚不该出门
Clear!
闪开!
Oh, my God.
噢 我的天啊
- She's... - Dead.
- 她... - 死了
I think.
我想是吧
Counting off 60 seconds.
倒数六十秒
Do you see any brain activity?
你有看到任何脑部活动吗?
I mean, something's going on, I'm not really sure what.
有事情发生 但我不确定是什么
It's recording, isn't it?
有在录影吧 对吗?
Yeah. Yeah.
有
- Fifty-one, 52... - Fifty-three...
- 五十一 五十二... - 五十三...
Fifty-four, 55, 56, 57,
五十四 五十五 五十六 五十七
fifty-eight, 59,
五十八 五十九
- sixty seconds. - Get her out.
- 六十秒 - 把她救活
Okay. Okay. Okay.
好
Blanket's warming.
毯子加热中
- What's her temp need to get to again? - Doesn't matter. Hurry up.
- 她的体温要达到几度? - 不重要 快点
Calm down.
冷静一下
- Charge 200. - Wait!
- 充电两百焦耳 - 等一下!
Clear!
闪开!
It's not working.
没有用
Of course it isn't.
当然没有用
Paddles are useless without a heart rhythm.
没有心律的话电击是没有用的
Didn't you listen to her?
你没听到她说的吗?
Yeah, I was gonna write down all the steps...
对 我要写下这些步骤...
Move! Just move.
走开!
Move!
(来人帮忙! 地下室C层 快点!)
Did we order an MRI on... Hey.
我们有要求核磁共振... 嘿
- Wait, what are you doing? - I...
- 等一下 你在做什么? - 我...
No, she needs an epi.
不 她需要肾上腺素
IV, you moron. God, it's already set up.
静脉注射 你这白痴 天啊 已经准备好了
Just push the drug into the goddamn arm!
把药推进去管子里!
Calm down! I got this.
冷静! 我在做了
God.
天啊
It's not working. Try something else!
没有用 试试看别的!
There is nothing else.
没有别的
Well, I...
呃 我...
What the fuck?
搞什么?
It was an experiment.
那是个实验
She had us stop her heart, and we can't get her back.
她的心跳停止了 我们无法让她回来
- How long has she been out? - I don't know, a couple of minutes.
- 她昏迷多久了? - 我不知道 有几分钟了吧
Look, I say we try the paddles.
听着 我们用电击板
No, no! Wait! Put them down.
不! 等一下! 放下来
I... Stop, stop.
我... 停
Take over for Sophia on the chest compressions.
接手苏菲亚的胸部按压
Do them much harder, get on top of her if it helps.
用力一点 如果必要的话坐在她身上
Sophia, put that cooling blanket on. She's too warm.
苏菲亚 把毯子温度调低 她太热了
Then charge the defib all the way to 360 and stand by.
充电除颤器到三百六十焦耳预备
As soon as Jamie and I get you a heartbeat,
只要杰米和我一测到心跳
however fluttering, you put those paddles on her
不论有多微弱 你把电击板放在她身上
and give her full power.
用最高能量
The blanket. Come on.
毯子 来吧
Got to push a lot more epi than what you've been doing.
肾上腺素要比现在使用的再多很多
Don't stop. Don't stop. Keep going.
别停 继续
All right.
好
Come on, Courtney.
快点 柯特
She's hypoxic.
她缺氧了
We need to intubate.
我们需要插管
All right? Go!
好吗? 快点!
Let's get it off.
拿下来
Help me.
帮我
BVM.
苏醒球
All right.
好
Go, go, go, go.
快
Clear!
闪开!
Courtney, can you hear me?
柯特妮 你听得到我吗?
You're crazy, you know that?
你疯了 你知道吗?
- You called Ray? - Were you getting it done?
- 你叫瑞来的吗? - 你有做好吗?
Does somebody want to fill me in here?
有人要告诉我发生什么事了吗?
It happened very gently.
它发生的过程很平缓
Like, almost like an untethering.
就像是绳子被解开一样
And I floated to the ceiling.
我飘浮到天花板
I could see my body. I could see Sophia and Jamie.
我可以看见我的身体 我可以看见苏菲亚和杰米
And then I could see the roof of the hospital.
然后我可以看见医院的屋顶
And I've never been up there.
我从没上去过那里
How do you explain that?
你要怎么解释?
I can't explain it.
我无法解释
Are you mad at us?
你生我们的气吗?
I don't know what to think
我不知道该怎么思考
other than you're all pretty stupid.
除了认为你们都很笨之外
She's lucky to be alive.
她很幸运可以活着
She's alive because of you.
她因为你才能活下来
What else happened?
还发生了什么事?
Did you see a white light?
你有看见白光吗?
I wouldn't call it that. It was...
我不会那样称呼 那是...
It was more like...
比较像是...
Pure energy.
纯粹的能量
And honestly, it was kind of sexual, actually.
老实说 有点性感
It was kind of sexual.
有点性感
Guys, playback's ready.
各位 播放就绪
Hey. Check this out.
嘿 来看一下
Okay, look. We're counting up from zero at the moment of death.
好 你看 我们从死亡时刻开始 由零往上数
Cognitive activity has ceased.
认知活动已经停止
Your heart stopped. No breathing, no pulse.
你的心跳停止 没有呼吸脉搏
We're 15 seconds in, and there.
我们在十五秒内 那里
Look at that.
你看
Like a bolt of lightning in your prefrontal cortex.
你的前额叶皮层像闪电一样
We might just be witnessing the afterlife, people.
各位 我们刚刚目击了来世
Okay.
好
Who knows what we're looking at?
谁知道我们在看什么?
We're not radiologists.
我们不是放射科医生
I mean, it could just be residual electricity.
我是说 这可能是剩余的电量
- You know, synapses shutting down. - Okay, we're moving on.
- 你知道 突触关闭 - 好 我们继续
So, you've been dead almost 40 seconds now,
所以你大概死了约四十秒
and look.
你看
This area lights up, the hippocampus.
这些区域发光 海马回
- That's not the hippocampus. - Of course it is.
- 那不是海马回 - 当然是
That is the ventral tegmental area.
那是腹侧被盖区域
It's the oldest part of the brain,
那是脑部最原始的部分
governs thirst, hunger, love.
掌管渴 饥和爱
Okay, doctors, I'm glad you're having fun.
好 医生 我很高兴你觉得很有趣
Got to get out of here.
该走了
Hey, Ray, come on.
嘿 瑞 拜托
Hey, no. Just let him go.
嘿 不 让他走吧
It's over. Her brain's just dark now.
结束了 她的头脑变黑暗了
- No. - Look at that.
- 不 - 你看那个
Wait. Amygdala.
等一下 是杏仁体
That's the amygdala. Rage.
那是杏仁体 愤怒
Stress. Emotional memory.
压力 情感记忆
Whatever you were seeing,
不管你看到什么
this is just before we pulled you out.
这都只是在我们把你救回来之前
Is she okay?
她还好吗?
She's been sitting there for, like, 10 minutes.
她已经坐在这里大概十分钟了
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的吗? - 对
What do you think she's doing out there?
你认为她在那里做什么?
I hope she doesn't try to fly.
我希望她不会想要飞
If there were brain chemicals released,
如果脑部有释放化学物质
the aftereffects could still be in her bloodstream.
后遗症会仍然存在她的血管里
I took LSD once.
我有一次吃了LSD迷幻药
I stayed awake for three days.
三天没睡觉
Shit.
该死
I'm gonna go check on her.
我要去查看她一下
Let's leave.
走吧
That's high.
好高
Hey.
嘿
Are you okay?
你还好吗?
I'm gonna bake some bread.
我要烤一点面包
What's with the bread?
这些面包是什么?
Courtney baked it. Six loaves, last night.
昨晚柯特妮烤了六条面包
She remembered her grandmother's recipe.
她记得她祖母的食谱
Also, she ran 12 miles.
还有 她跑了十九公里
- Twelve miles? - Let's begin.
- 十九公里? - 开始吧
We've been ramping up Michael Evergreen with meds for ten hours,
我们给麦克艾佛葛林 十小时的药物
and his epilepsy hasn't gotten any better.
而他的癫痫症没有比较好
Now he's developed a skin rash.
他现在却有皮肤过敏
It's a mystery. The meds should be working.
真是无法理解 药应该会有效的
Carbamazepine?
卡马西平?
What?
什么?
Carbamazepine has an 11% chance of reacting negatively
卡马西平有百分之十一的无效机率
with lamotrigine, which is the other drug
乐命达是另一种药
- that Michael's on. - Seriously?
- 是麦克在服用的 - 你说真的吗?
Good catch, Courtney.
柯特妮 接得好
Sophia, next case.
苏菲亚 下一个案子
Adele Gunther. 44 years old. Admitted with mild confusion.
阿黛儿刚瑟 四十四岁 被诊断有轻微的精神错乱
Says her sister's an impostor, she doesn't recognize her.
说她姐妹是骗子 她不记得她
No history of trauma. Too young for dementia.
没有创伤历史 太年轻不至于失智
We're gonna send it out to Psychiatry for...
我们要把她送去心理部门...
It's Capgras syndrome.
是卡普格拉综合症
- Go on. - Capgras is an impairment
- 继续 - 卡普格拉是一种
of the brain's facial recognition center.
脑部脸部辨识中心的损伤
And a very rare diagnosis.
是一个非常罕见的诊断
V.S. Ramachandran, in his book, Phantoms of the Brain,
维莱亚努尔拉马钱德兰在他的书 《脑部魅影》中提到
links frontal cortex dichotomies, like this, to Capgras.
链接额叶皮质二分法 就像卡普格拉
That's not on this year's syllabus.
那不是今年的课程
Optional reading in my first year.
我第一年的选修课外读物
Well, that's more like it.
那还差不多
My sister loved this piece.
我妹妹很爱这首歌
Drug warnings for carbamazepine run 20 pages long.
卡马西平的药性警告有二十页这么多
How could she possibly recall a detail like that?
她怎么可能想起像那样的细节?
How is she playing the piano again, after 12 years?
她是如何在十二年后再次弹钢琴的?
She's not playing that well.
她弹得没那么好
It's like her brain's been rewired,
就像是他的脑部被倒带了
accessing everything she's ever learned.
出现所有她学过的事
I don't care what happened to her.
我不在乎她发生什么事
This experiment needs to end right now.
这个实验现在必须终止
I'm not gonna risk everything for a morbid fascination you guys have.
我不会因为你们的 病态迷恋而赌上一切
You think you're all medical pioneers?
你以为你们是医界先锋吗?
You're just a bunch of rich kids screwing around,
你们只是一群捣蛋的有钱孩子们
before you become wealthy specialists
在你们变成富有的专科医师之前
with your Ivy League bumper stickers on your Mercedes.
你们的宾士的保险杆上贴着常春藤名校贴纸
I was with you until the end.
我是陪你走到最后的人
No one puts bumper stickers on a Mercedes.
没人在宾士的保险杆上贴贴纸
I think we're way past parlor tricks here.
我想我们的程度 远超过廉价的魔术把戏
That does it. I'm going next.
就这样 我是下一位
- Okay. - Tonight. I am.
- 好 - 今晚换我
And you're all gonna be there.
你们都要在场
It's a good day to die.
今天是死掉的好日子
No! No!
不!
Jesus Christ.
老天啊
Is that what I looked like?
我看起来像那样吗?
Yep. Exactly like that.
对 一模一样
- I knew you'd show up. - How long has he been under?
- 我就知道你会出现 - 已经这种状态多久了?
Forty-five seconds.
四十五秒了
I thought you'd had it with all this foolishness.
我以为你认为这些是愚蠢的
Jamie asked me to be here.
杰米叫我来的
He wanted me to pull him out.
他要我把他带回来
- Pause compressions. - One, two, three...
- 暂停按压 - 一 二 三...
- Still no heartbeat. - Pushing epi.
- 还是没心跳 - 注射肾上腺素
- Come on, Jamie, wake up. - He can't hear you.
- 快点 杰米 醒醒 - 他听不到你
Sophia, get ready to intubate.
苏菲亚 准备插管
Okay. I've never done this before,
好 我以前从没做过
- so just give me a second... - Just do it!
- 给我一点时间... - 快点!
Ray, relax. There's no need to panic.
瑞 放轻松 别慌
Let's give the epi a second to work.
给肾上腺素一点时间去发挥作用
Jamie...
杰米...
Clear!
闪开!
Take it out, take it out.
拿出来
Hey...
嘿...
Jamie, Jamie, Jamie.
杰米
I need a drink.
我需要喝一杯
Shots, shots, shots!
喝!
Yeah, come on.
对 快点
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- 干杯! - 干杯!
What do you guys think about taking this wall down?
你们认为把这座墙拆下来如何?
- No, no, no. - I've always wanted a loft.
- 不 - 我一直想要一个阁楼
It's hailing! Courtney!
下冰雹了! 柯特妮!
What?
什么?
Watch it.
小心
This is crazy.
这真是疯狂
It's like they're on the same wavelength.
好像他们两个有相同的波长
We should bottle flatlining, sell it as a club drug.
我们应该把死亡游戏装瓶 然后当毒品卖给俱乐部
Here. Use this.
来 用这个
- Hey, no, no. - No, no, no.
- 嘿 不 - 不
Oh, my God.
噢 我的天啊
This has been the strangest night of my life.
今晚是我这一生中最奇怪的夜晚
You going next, Ray?
瑞 你是下一个吗?
What, flatlining? No way.
什么 死亡游戏吗? 不可能
I'd bring you back out.
我会带你回来
Maybe.
或许吧
You have to admit, I was pretty good with that defibrillator.
你必须承认 我对那个除颤器还蛮拿手的
You were okay.
还好而已
Would it kill you to admit that I might be just as good a doctor as you?
承认我可能像你一样是位好医生 你会死吗?
I never said you were not.
我从来没说过你不是
Hey, Marlo, your brother's here.
嘿 玛洛 你哥哥来了
You have no more experience than the rest of us.
你比我们其他人都还更没经验
I do.
我有
I was a firefighter in Houston.
我在休士顿时当过消防员
Almost six years.
当了快六年
I'm going next.
下一个是我
It was super fun.
超级好玩的
I was all-powerful. I had the whole city to myself.
我独揽大权 这个城市都是我的
It's weird, isn't it?
很奇怪 不是吗?
I thought there'd be more people, like...
我以为会有更多的人 像是...
Aren't you supposed to see...
你不是应该去看...
Family members who've died, or...
死去的家人吗 或者是...
Maybe there's no one there because it wasn't really our time.
或许没人在那里 因为我们的死期还没到
Was it all fun?
一直都很好玩吗?
What do you mean?
你是什么意思?
I don't... I mean, like, was there anything disturbing or...
我不是... 我是说 有什么让人不安的事或者...
Not really.
没有
Why?
怎么了?
Nothing.
没事
She's stabilizing.
她稳定下来了
I don't understand, the data shows her starting
我不懂 数据显示她开始
into a massive seizure, and then it just went away.
进入大规模的癫痫发作 然后就消失不见了
I gave her Ativan.
我给了她萝拉西泮
On whose authority?
是谁授权的?
I'm sorry. I'll get approval next time.
对不起 我下次会先得到授权
You saved her life.
你救了她的命
Yes, I did.
是的 没错
I'm Jesus.
我是耶稣
Everyone I touch today, I'm gonna heal.
今天我所碰过的人 都被我治愈了
You know, it's funny, because you and Courtney both flat...
你知道 很有趣 因为你跟柯特妮两个人都...
You both flatlined,
你们都经历过死亡游戏
yet Courtney is focused on the past,
柯特妮专注在过去
memories, recipes.
记忆和食谱
Whereas you, you're focused on the present, using your intuition.
而你 却专注在现在 使用你的直觉
What does that have in common with Courtney?
那跟柯特妮有什么共同点呢?
Sophia, Marlo, you're needed in the ICU.
苏菲亚 玛洛 加护病房需要你们
It's an awakening.
他们觉醒了
See you later, Jesus.
耶稣 待会见
- An awakening? - Yeah.
- 觉醒? - 对
You here for the abortion?
你是来堕胎的吗?
Should Ernesto La Paz get morphine?
可以给埃内斯托拉巴斯一点吗啡吗?
I'll check with the resident.
我跟驻院医生确认一下
Sophia? Where are you going?
苏菲亚? 你要去哪里?
It's 11:30 at night.
现在是晚上十一点三十分
You're not on call, and you don't have anything scheduled.
你没有待命 也没有安排做什么事
No, I'm going to the library.
不 我要去图书馆
I'm just gonna do some more studying.
我只是需要再多读点书
No, no, no, no.
不
I'm making tea, and we're gonna start reviewing
过来泡茶 我们要来复习
all of the terminology for the nervous system.
神经系统中所有的术语
- But I... - Now.
- 但是我... - 现在
Okay.
好
Where's Sophia?
苏菲亚在哪里?
We need to start. It's already 12:15.
我们要快点开始 已经十二点十五分了
This isn't gonna hurt, is it?
这不会痛吧 是吗?
The anesthesia will take care of that.
有打麻醉就不会
Three minutes.
三分钟
Well, Jamie only did two.
呃 杰米只做了两分钟
What can I say?
我能说什么?
I'm competitive.
我爱竞争
After my three minutes are done,
在我的三分钟时间到了之后
these are the interventions I want, in their specific order.
这些是我要的干预措施 有他们特定的顺序
If I don't come out right away, I want you to intubate me.
如果我无法马上回来 我要你们帮我插管
Force the oxygen, okay?
强行灌入氧气 好吗?
Hey, I'm gonna bring you out of it.
嘿 我会带你回来的
Relax. Enjoy the experience.
放轻松 享受这个经验
Okay, okay.
好
Infusion's flowing.
输液注入
She's out. Body temp's 94.
她没意识了 体温三十四度
Charging 200.
充电两百焦耳
Clear.
闪开
Asystole.
心搏停止
(凶手)
38-year-old male, stung in the face by a jellyfish.
三十八岁男性 被水母叮咬脸部
by a jellyfish.
被水母
That's it. Let's get her out.
时间到了 把她带回来
Epi in.
肾上腺素注入
- Defib! - Charge to 200.
- 去颤! - 充电两百焦耳
Clear.
闪开
- No pulse. - Damn it, we just had it.
- 没有脉搏 - 该死 差一点就成功了
Juice her again.
再次给她输液注入
I'm gonna push an epi and sodium bicarb.
我要注入肾上腺素和碳酸氢钠
Defib. She's not stabilizing.
去颤 她尚未稳定
Charge 300.
充电三百焦耳
Clear. Come on.
闪开 快点
No pulse.
没有脉搏
This is not working. I need to intubate.
这没有用 我需要插管
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
嘿
Calm down. I got this.
冷静 有我在
360. Clear.
三百六十焦耳 闪开
Please.
拜托
She's back.
她回来了
You good? You're all right.
你还好吗? 你没事
- Yeah. - There you go.
- 对 - 来
We're safe. No one ever comes up here.
我们安全了 没有人会来这里
- It's so beautiful. - Isn't it?
- 好美 - 不是吗?
Her temp's low.
她的体温很低
Pulse still racing.
脉搏持续上升
Well, I think three minutes is too long.
我想三分钟太久了
Look, she had a bad trip, it happens.
听着 她这趟不顺利 有时候会这样
What, you're an expert?
怎样 你是专家吗?
Yeah, more than you.
对 我比你还懂
- Is she okay? - Where have you been?
- 她没事吧? - 你去哪里了?
- Marlo is fine. - Yeah, I'll be okay.
- 玛洛没事 - 对 我会没事的
I'm going next. Right now.
下一个换我 就是现在
- Right now? - Why not?
- 现在吗? - 有何不可?
The cleaning crew is gonna be down there in like 20 minutes.
清洁人员二十分钟后就会下来这里
- Okay. - No, we've gone too far.
- 好 - 不 我们越界太多
No more flatlining.
不可以再玩死亡游戏了
Okay, so you three get to expand your consciousness
好 所以你们三个可以扩展你们的意识
and get academic advantage, but I don't?
并得到学术上的优势 那我就不行吗?
Advantage.
优势
You think this makes you better, Sophia?
苏菲亚 你认为这会使你更好吗?
This makes you dead.
这会让你死亡
You have much more sense than that.
你应该更清楚的
Ray, if this bothers you so much, then just walk away.
瑞 如果你这么困扰 你可以离开
- Well, maybe I should. - You're not going anywhere.
- 或许我应该离开 - 你哪里都不能去
You're in this as deep as the rest of us.
你跟我们其他的人一样涉入太深
Okay, look, I don't care how dangerous this is.
好 听着 我不在乎这有多危险
I need this more than any of you guys.
我比你们任何人都更需要这个
Ray, it's her decision. Just like it was each of ours.
瑞 那是她的决定 就像我们每个人一样
If Sophia wants to do this, then we're doing it tonight.
如果苏菲亚想要这么做 我们就要今晚来做
Just don't stay in too long.
只是不要逗留太久
A B-plus on a biology exam is not acceptable.
生物学考试只有八十几分是无法接受的
Not acceptable.
无法接受
That will not get you into a top-10 medical school.
那样的话你没办法进入前十名的医学院
(计时器-计时中 一点零七分五十二秒)
Someone's coming down the elevator.
有人搭电梯下来了
- What? - Get her out.
- 什么? - 带她回来
Come on, come on, come on.
快点
Let's go. Let's go!
快点!
Pushing an amp of epi.
注入一安瓶的肾上腺素
Where the hell are you going?
你要去哪里?
Start compressions.
开始施压
Please, God, bring her back.
拜托 神啊 带她回来
Good thinking, Doctor.
医生 不错的想法
I'm sure that's gonna help.
我确定那会有帮助的
Epi in.
肾上腺素注入
Pause compressions.
暂停加压
Clear.
闪开
Irina.
伊琳娜
You are not the only kid that is out there trying to get in.
你不是唯一在外面想进来的孩子
(火灾警报器)
Shit.
该死
One, two, three.
一 二 三
- V-tach. - Charging 360.
- 室性心动过速 - 充电三百焦耳
Clear.
闪开
We got her, we got her. Let's go, let's go. Come on.
有脉搏了 快点
We're gonna get you out of here.
我们会把你带回来
You're gonna be okay.
你会没事的
- Come on, you'll be okay. Come here. - Come on.
- 来吧 你会没事的 - 快点
- Come on! - I got her, I got her.
- 快点! - 她有脉搏了
- My jacket, my jacket. - Got it.
- 我的外套 - 拿到了
Go, go.
快走
Okay. To the right.
往右边
It's open. Just get in.
是开的 快进去
- Okay. - Okay, okay.
- 好 - 好
Should you really be driving?
真的应该由你来开车吗?
Wait!
等一下!
Shit!
该死!
You asshole! You left us.
你这个混蛋! 你把我们留下来
- Are you okay? - The hell I did.
- 你还好吗? - 我有才怪
- I saved your asses. - Let's go!
- 我救了你们 - 快走!
- Here they come! - Hold it right there!
- 他们来了 - 站住!
We got to get out of here!
我们要离开这里!
Hold on!
等一下!
We're going too fast!
我们开太快了!
Oh, my God.
噢 我的天啊
- Shit! - Car!
- 该死! - 有车!
God!
天啊!
Watch out!
小心!
Oh, my God!
噢 我的天啊!
It's not funny.
这一点也不有趣
Here we go.
我们来了
Where are we going?
我们要去哪里?
Hell yeah.
一点也没错
Courtney!
柯特妮!
Come.
来
Look, I don't know if
听着 我不知道是否是
it's the experience of dying and coming back again,
濒死经验再度的返回
but I have got a really intense craving right now.
但我现在有一个强烈的渴望
For what, gelato?
什么 意式冰淇淋吗?
No.
不是
Oh, my God, this is crazy!
噢 我的天 这真是疯狂!
Sophia.
苏菲亚
Sophia, open this door!
苏菲亚 把门打开!
I think there's someone at the door.
我想有人在门边
- Sophia! - I don't care.
- 苏菲亚! - 我不管
Don't stop.
别停下来
Sophia, I need you to open this door.
苏菲亚 我需要你把门打开
Sophia!
苏菲亚!
It's nice to meet you, Mrs. Manning.
曼宁太太 很高兴见到你
How dare you bring someone back to my apartment.
你好大胆子敢带人回来我的公寓
I'm moving out.
我要搬出去
- What did you say? - I'm finding my own place.
- 你说什么? - 我要自己找地方住
You will do no such thing.
你不可以这样做
See, it doesn't matter what you say, Mom.
妈 不管你说什么
Whatever threats you make. I'm 25 years old.
不管你威胁什么 我二十五岁了
Succeed or fail...
成功或失败...
I'm doing it on my own.
我都要靠自己
Good night.
晚安
All right.
好
Good night.
晚安
How are you getting home?
你要怎么回家?
There's a metro stop nearby.
附近有地铁
Look, there's something I need to tell you.
听着 我有事情要告诉你
It's important.
很重要
So, you gonna tell me or what?
你到底要不要告诉我?
I killed someone.
我杀了人
What?
什么?
It was two months ago.
大概两个月前
It was my ER rotation.
我在急诊室的轮班时
The patient's name was Cyrus Gudgeon.
病人的名字叫做塞洛斯葛吉恩
He was admitted for a jellyfish sting.
他被判定为水母叮伤
Cyrus Gudgeon. Yeah, I remember. He got stung in the face.
塞洛斯葛吉恩 对 我记得 他的脸被叮到
Died of shock, right?
死于休克 对吗?
No, he died because of a mistake that I made.
不 他是因为我犯的错误才死的
I gave him epi and Benadryl.
我给了他肾上腺素和苯海拉明
But those two drugs don't cross-react.
但这两种药不会有交互作用产生
He had metoprolol in his system.
他的身体里有着美托洛尔
He basically suffocated to death.
基本上他是窒息而死
I'd been on duty for, like, 36 hours,
我已经值班了三十六个小时
and I must have screwed up and forgotten to ask him
我一定是搞砸了忘了问他
if he was taking any medications.
他是否有服用任何药物
He would be alive right now if it wasn't for my mistake.
如果不是我的错他就不会死
Why are you telling me this?
你为什么要告诉我这些?
Because I saw him.
因为我看到他了
Cyrus. I saw him in my flatline.
塞洛斯 我在死亡游戏中见到他
And it must mean something, right?
那一定有什么意义 对吗?
Hey, mistakes happen to everybody.
嘿 大家都会犯错
Yeah, but I work so hard every single day.
对 但我每天这么认真的工作
- I do the right thing. - I'm sure you do.
- 我做对的事 - 我相信你是
- I'm not a bad person. - No, you're not.
- 我不是坏人 - 对 你不是
I'm not a bad person. I...
我不是坏人 我...
- Everything's gonna be fine, Marlo. - No, I'm scared.
- 玛洛 一切都会没事的 - 不 我好害怕
I'm scared.
我好害怕
Wait, wait, wait.
等一下
You... You can't just...
你... 你不能就...
I'm... I'm sorry.
我... 我很抱歉
Yeah, what am I doing with you?
对 我跟你在这里做什么?
- I got to go right now. I'm sorry. No... - No. No, no, no, wait.
- 我必须现在离开 对不起 不... - 不 等一下
- Damn, you have so many. - Just...
- 该死的 你穿这么多 - 只是...
Okay, okay.
好
I got it, I got it.
我懂了
Courtney!
柯特妮!
Help!
救命!
Help! Tessa!
救命! 泰莎!
Tessa!
泰莎!
Help!
救命!
My sister!
我的妹妹!
Help!
救命
My sister!
我的妹妹!
- My sister. - Come on.
- 我的妹妹 - 快点
No! My sister!
不! 我的妹妹!
Tessa! My... Tessa!
泰莎! 我的... 泰莎!
No!
不!
I hope this doesn't become awkward.
我希望这不会变得很怪
Too late.
太迟了
I can't imagine what you must think of me.
我不敢想像你对我的看法
Why?
为什么?
Well, first I tell you that I'm responsible
首先我告诉了你我要为
for the death of a patient,
一位死去的病人负责
and then I go and totally attack you.
然后我又跟你上床
I mean, seriously, what...
我是说 老实说 你...
What do you see in me?
你怎么看我的?
You're really hot.
你很辣
Shut up.
闭嘴
I got to go.
我要走了
Yeah.
好
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was four months into our first year.
我们医学院第一年的第四个月时
You were assisting at the oncology ward.
你在肿瘤病房协助
A breast cancer patient was there for her first round of chemo.
一位乳癌病人第一次去那里做化疗
She was anxious and scared, but you sat down and calmed her
她很担心又害怕 你坐在她身边安慰她
by asking about her kids, her job.
问到她的孩子 她的工作
You were so kind.
你很仁慈
You didn't think anyone was watching,
你以为没人看到
but I was watching you through the door.
但我从门后看到了一切
Three hours later, I stopped by,
三小时后 我经过
and you were there checking on her again.
你又在那里检查她
That's what I see in you.
我是这么看你的
Jamie?
杰米?
Courtney? What's going on?
柯特妮? 怎么了?
I saw my sister.
我看见我妹妹了
What?
什么?
At the waterfront.
在滨水处
It was her.
是她
I saw my dead sister.
我看见我死去的妹妹
Where... Where are you?
你... 你在哪里?
I'm home.
我在家
I don't understand what's happening.
我不懂发生什么事了
Stay there.
留在家里
I'm coming over.
我来找你
I just... I miss my sister.
我只是... 我想念我妹妹
I should have told you all that
我应该全都告诉你
this wasn't about
这跟科学或发现
science or discovery.
无关
I think I'm going crazy.
我想我要疯了
Like I'm seeing things.
我好像看见了什么东西
Something I did.
我做过的事
It was my fault.
那是我的错
I'm sorry.
对不起
Tessa?
泰莎?
Tessa, is that really you?
泰莎 真的是你吗?
Tessa, are you okay?
泰莎 你还好吗?
- What are you? - Courtney!
- 你是什么东西? - 柯特妮!
Courtney!
柯特妮!
(早上六点三十分)
Let's go!
快点!
(早上十点三十二分)
(医院-请回电 医院-未接来电)
(医院-紧急请回电)
Hi. An update on room four.
嗨 四号房要更新资料
We've given the Lasix bolus, and the output is limited.
我们给了来适泄注射液 而输出剂量有限
It's been less than 50 cc's in the last two hours.
过去两小时中不到五十毫升
All right.
好
They found her at the bottom of a fire escape.
他们在逃生梯的底部发现她
We'll know more after the autopsy,
验尸后会知道更多
but right now, it's unclear whether she fell,
但是现在 不清楚她是摔下去的
jumped, or God knows what.
跳下去的 或是其他原因
I know you all liked her.
我知道你们都喜欢她
And I'm sorry, but for now, I need you
对不起 但是现在 我需要你们
to pick up her patient load and divide it amongst yourselves.
帮我消化病人数量 你们自己分病人
We still have a hospital to run.
我们还是要经营医院
Do any of you know what might have been going on with her?
你们有人知道她到底发生了什么事吗?
Is there something you're not telling me?
你们有事没告诉我吗?
All right.
好
It just doesn't feel real.
这感觉不真实
I know.
我知道
You know, I can't believe she's gone.
我不敢相信她不在了
We need to talk.
我们要聊一下
Okay, something is happening to us, and my mind is playing tricks on me.
好 我们有事发生在我们身上 我的头脑正在玩弄我
This morning, when I was swimming in the pool...
今天早上 当我在泳池里游泳时...
I can't talk, okay?
我不能谈 好吗?
- I have rounds right now. - Guys,
- 我现在要去巡房 - 各位
Wolfson already knows we're holding something back.
沃夫森已经知道我们的疑虑
The school is going to investigate her death.
学校要调查她的死因
I don't believe it was a suicide.
我不相信那是自杀事件
Maybe she fell.
她或许是摔下来
You were there.
你当时在那边
What happened?
发生什么事了?
She never answered the door.
她从来没开门
I figured... She went to bed.
我以为... 她去睡了
Hey, killer party?
嘿 杀手派对吗?
You all look like shit.
你们都看起来很糟糕
Hey, listen,
嘿 听着
if the school finds out we have been flatlining,
如果学校发现我们在玩死亡游戏
we will be expelled.
我们都会被开除
And you can say goodbye to your future.
你们就可以跟未来道别了
Any notes you've taken, destroy them.
你们有做任何的笔记 都要销毁
I'm gonna get into Courtney's apartment, get her phone, computer,
我要去柯特妮的公寓拿她的电话和电脑
anything incriminating.
所有的罪证
You know, you were right this whole time, Ray.
你知道吗 瑞 你一直都是对的
We should've listened to you.
我们当初应该听你的
Yeah, that's true.
对 没错
This isn't on you, man.
老兄 这跟你无关
You should just walk away.
应该离我们远一点
We'll keep your name out of it.
我们会把你的名字排除在外
No.
不
I'm not going anywhere.
我哪里都不去
Whatever happens to all of you happens to me.
你们承担什么后果 我也会一起承担
- Yes? - Hey.
- 喂? - 嘿
Look, bad news.
听着 坏消息
Ray and I checked her apartment.
瑞和我去查了她的公寓
We found her computer and some notes,
我们发现了她的电脑和一些笔记
- but not her phone. - Campus security
- 但是没有她的电话 - 校园警卫
- could have gotten there before you. - Okay.
- 可能在你们到之前就过去了 - 好
Assuming you're right and it's not a criminal investigation,
假设你是对的 这不是一桩犯罪调查
then all that stuff stays with her body.
所有的东西跟她的尸体在一起
Meaning you can go down there and look for it.
表示你可以下去下面把它找出来
Go down where?
下去哪里?
Where do you think? The goddamn morgue.
你觉得是哪里? 该死的停尸间
(打给柯特妮)
Okay.
好
(柯特妮荷姆斯)
(凶手)
(柯特妮来电)
Marlo.
玛洛
Marlo?
玛洛?
Jamie...
杰米...
Jamie.
杰米
Like I'm seeing things.
我好像看见了什么东西
Something I did.
我所做过的事情
It was my fault.
都是我的错
I'm sorry.
对不起
Tessa?
泰莎?
Tessa, is that really you?
泰莎 真的是你吗?
Are you okay?
你还好吗?
What are you?
你是什么东西?
Jesus Christ.
我的老天啊
What was that?
那是什么东西?
She was talking to someone.
她在跟别人讲话
Someone was there.
有人在那边
You don't know that.
你不能确定
She could've been hallucinating.
她可能产生了幻觉
It didn't sound like that to me.
我觉得听起来不像
What if it was Tessa?
如果是泰莎呢?
What do you mean?
你是什么意思?
She saw something. You heard her.
她看见了什么 你听到她说了
She said that she did something.
她说过她做了一些事
Something was her fault.
有些事是她的错
What if that's it? What if...
如果就是那样呢? 如果...
What if our sins are coming for us?
如果我们犯的罪来找我们了呢?
Sins. That's ridiculous.
罪 真是荒谬
So, what are we gonna do?
那我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办?
We're gonna tell each other the goddamn truth.
我们要将事实告诉彼此
That's what we're gonna do.
我们就应该这么做
There's a girl I... I used to know.
有一位... 我认识的女孩
Alicia.
艾莉西亚
She was a waitress at my dad's country club.
她是我爸乡村俱乐部的女服务生
Oh, my God.
噢 我的天啊
- You killed her? - What? No.
- 你杀了她吗? - 什么? 不是
No, I did not kill anyone.
我没有杀任何人
I...
我...
I... I...
I got her pregnant.
我让她怀孕了
I wanted to help, you know?
我想要帮忙 你懂吗?
Pay for the abortion, be... Go with her for the procedure.
付钱去堕胎和... 陪她一起去做手术
Anyway, the... The day came,
反正 到了... 那一天
and I... I couldn't deal with it.
我... 无法面对事实
I... I drove right past.
我... 没下车
I left her to fend for herself.
我让她自己一个人面对
And she showed up in your flatline?
而她出现在你的死亡游戏中吗?
I wish that was all.
我希望只有那样而已
She showed up last night, too.
她昨晚也出现了
So you're being haunted by somebody that's alive.
所以你被活着的人纠缠
- What are you talking about? - This.
- 你在说什么? - 这个
I am talking about this.
我说的是这个
Alicia did this to me.
艾莉西亚对我做了这件事
Only it wasn't her.
但是这不是她
Just like it wasn't Courtney's sister.
就如同那不是柯特妮的妹妹一样
Then what was it?
那么它是什么?
Jamie, what?
杰米 什么?
I... I don't know.
我... 我不知道
Something feeding off our guilty conscience.
有东西啃食着我们罪恶的良知
What do you mean? Like...
你是什么意思? 像是...
Something demonic?
恶魔的东西吗?
Maybe it's using our pasts, our sins.
或许它在利用我们的过去和我们的罪恶
Wait, wait.
等一下
We're rational people here.
我们是理性的人
You could have stabbed yourself.
你可能会自残
People on drugs hurt themselves all the time.
使用毒品的人常常伤害他们自己
There has to be a logical explanation.
一定会有个理性的解释
I was 17.
我当时十七岁
Her name was Irina Wong, and she had a higher GPA than I did,
她叫做伊琳娜王 她的在校平均成绩比我高
so I hacked her text messages
所以我黑进了她的简讯里
and I sent her naked photos to the whole class.
我把她的裸照传给全班
It destroyed her.
这件事毁了她
What is the point in confessing all of this?
你现在坦承这些事有什么用?
This is clearly just happening here.
很明显的这些是刚刚才发生
- That thing... - Look, look, Courtney said to me
- 那件事... - 听着 柯特妮对我说
she thinks maybe we opened a door.
她认为或许我们开了一扇门
Wait, so you knew?
等一下 所以你知道吗?
You and Courtney knew there was a downside to flatlining,
你和柯特妮知道死亡游戏有缺点
and... And you still let me and Marlo go in?
而... 你仍然让我和玛洛加入?
Hey, look, I thought it was just part of the experience.
嘿 听着 我以为这都是经验的一部分
Side effects may include
副作用包含了
dry mouth, hallucinations, existential dread.
口干 幻觉 存在恐惧
I did not know that the side effects would show up
我不知道副作用会出现
and start hunting us down.
然后开始纠缠我们
There is a scientific explanation to all of this.
对所有的一切有科学解释
We're way beyond explanations.
发生在我们身上的事情 早就超过了科学解释
Okay.
好
If Courtney was right,
如果柯特妮是对的
whatever's happening to us,
不管发生在我们身上的什么事情
these hallucinations, these hauntings, whatever it is,
这些幻觉 这些纠缠 不管是什么
it's only gonna get worse.
只会越来越糟
Until we figure it out,
一直到我们想出方法
until we figure out what to do,
一直到我们知道该怎么做
whatever killed her is gonna kill all of us, too.
不管是什么东西杀了她 也会杀了我们
Note the negative mass effect secondary to the encephalomalacia.
注意负质量效应继发于脑炎
There are multiple foci of high T2 and FLAIR signal intensity
在上层白质中 有多个高度T2和闪光
in the supratentorial white matter.
信号强度焦点
These findings are nonspecific, but most in keeping with
这些发现是非特异性的 但是大部分跟
chronic microangiopathic changes.
慢性微血管病变有关
You'll note there's no hydrocephalus.
你可以注意到没有脑积水
There's no brain herniation. The vessels are well seen.
没有脑部症状 血管清晰可见
(未知-你这小贱货 我不敢相信你跟他睡了)
You'll note that the gray matter
你可以注意到灰色物质
differentiation is completely maintained.
区别部分完全的被维持住
You little slut. I can't believe you slept with him.
你这小贱货 我不敢相信你跟他睡了
Not only are you a hopeless grind,
你不只是一个毫无希望的人
but you're an immature, whiney, crybaby bitch.
你还是个幼稚 爱发牢骚 爱哭的婊子
- Okay, stop! - Excuse me?
- 好 停下来! - 你说什么?
Sorry. Sorry.
抱歉
No.
不
No! No! No!
不!
No!
No.
不
Stop!
停下来!
Stop! No!
停下来! 不!
No!
不!
Stop! No!
停下来! 不!
Hey.
嘿
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么?
Have you seen Cyrus Gudgeon lately?
你最近有见到塞洛斯葛吉恩吗?
If that's supposed to be a joke,
如果那是个玩笑
- it's not funny. - It's not a joke.
- 不好笑 - 那不是玩笑
Then what?
那是什么?
I pulled the autopsy report.
我拿出了验尸报告
It says nothing about metoprolol.
上面写着跟美托洛尔一点也无关
So then I went back to the original path lab notes of the blood test,
所以我去看血液测试的原始 实验室笔记
and there it was.
就在那里
Metoprolol.
美托洛尔
I'm going inside.
我要进去了
Why wouldn't the autopsy report match with the notes, Marlo?
玛洛 验尸报告跟笔记为何不符?
Marlo?
玛洛?
Marlo.
Did you change that autopsy report?
你窜改了验尸报告吗?
I had to protect myself.
我必须保护我自己
Protect yourself? Really?
保护你自己? 真的吗?
By making it look like he died from a sting
让他看起来像是死于被叮咬
and not a drug you administered?
而不是你治疗他的药物吗?
I know.
我知道
- I know. It was wrong of me. - You got to tell someone.
- 我知道 我错了 - 你必须告诉别人
- I am. I'm telling you. - The dean, Marlo.
- 我告诉你了 - 玛洛 要告诉院长
You have to tell the dean you changed that report.
你必须告诉院长你窜改了报告
Why?
为什么?
- What good is that gonna do now? - Really?
- 现在说这些有什么用吗? - 真的吗?
You don't see it?
你看不出来吗?
It's your flatline, Cyrus Gudgeon.
是你的死亡游戏 塞洛斯葛吉恩
You know, it was so nice being with you
你知道 跟你在一起很好
and realizing, after all this time, that you actually like me.
在这么久之后 终于了解到你喜欢我
And now you have to go and spoil it.
但你现在却必须来摧毁它
- I am here because I like you. - Yeah, well, it's easy for you.
- 我在这里是因为我喜欢你 - 对 你说的容易
You don't have to sacrifice anything.
你不用牺牲任何事情
I'm becoming a doctor with a degree from a top medical school.
我是从顶尖医学院拿到学位 成为医生的
I've worked my whole life for this.
我花了一辈子的时间就是为了这个
And now, I... I made one mistake. I mean, admitting it
但是现在 我... 我只犯了一个错 我是说 承认错误
is not gonna bring the guy back.
并不会让那家伙起死回生
All it's gonna do is end my career.
只会毁了我的事业
That is the point here,
说到重点了
your career.
你的事业
If you were willing to change an autopsy report, then...
如果你愿意窜改验尸报告 那么...
Say it.
说吧
Then maybe you shouldn't be a doctor.
那么你或许不应该当医生
Hi. Is this Beverly Wong?
嗨 这里是贝弗利王的家吗?
Beverly Wong from East Hadley?
东哈德利的贝弗利王吗?
It is?
是吗?
Do you have a daughter named Irina?
你有一位叫做伊琳娜的女儿吗?
Hey.
嘿
Thanks for coming with me.
谢谢你跟我来
Could you have rented a smaller car?
你一定要租这么小的车吗?
You're sure it's the same Irina?
你确定是同一位伊琳娜吗?
Irina.
伊琳娜
Yes.
对
It's Sophia.
我是苏菲亚
From East Hadley.
东哈德利高中
We went to the same high school.
我们是高中同学
I'm sorry. I know, it... It's... It's been forever.
对不起 我知道 这... 已经很久了
I...
我...
I really needed to talk to you, so I was hoping we could sit down...
我真的需要跟你谈一下 我希望我们可以坐下来...
What is this about?
你想说什么?
You never knew this, but...
你从不知道这件事 但是...
I was the one who sent your pictures to the whole class.
是我把你的照片传给全班的
That was me.
就是我
I can't stand myself to think about it.
光是想到这件事我就无法忍受我自己
Bottom line, it was an awful thing to do. I know that.
结果 这是我做的一件很糟糕的事 我知道
What do you want?
你要什么?
I'd like you to accept my apology.
我希望你接受我的道歉
It's not necessary.
不需要了
Okay? I've moved on.
好吗? 我已经忘记那些不愉快的事了
Irina... This is important, okay?
伊琳娜... 这很重要 好吗?
I am so sorry.
我很抱歉
Irina, please.
伊琳娜 拜托
Sophia.
苏菲亚
I forgive you.
我原谅你
Thank you.
谢谢你
What'd she say?
她说了什么?
Hey, Marlo, it's Jamie.
嘿 玛洛 我是杰米
- Hey. - Look, we're just kind of riffing here,
- 嘿 - 听着 我们在这里反反覆覆
but maybe you find whoever you've wronged,
但是或许你找到有所亏欠的那个人
whatever you're feeling guilty about,
不管你觉得有什么罪恶
and you take responsibility.
你负责了
I mean, look, who knows if it'll work?
我是说 听着 有谁知道那是否有用?
But what have we got to lose?
但对我们来说有什么损失呢?
Alicia!
艾莉西亚!
Alicia.
艾莉西亚
Hey. It's... It's me.
嘿 是... 是我
It's Jamie.
是杰米
What are you doing here, Jamie?
杰米 你在这里做什么?
He's your son?
他是你儿子吗?
Hey. Hey... I came to apologize.
嘿... 我是来道歉的
For taking off on you.
因为我丢下你
I... I panicked. I was a coward.
我... 我慌了 我是个懦夫
I should have been there for you.
我应该陪你一起的
But you weren't.
但你并没有这么做
Look, I...
听着 我...
I want to make amends.
我想要补偿
Do what's right.
做正确的事
Help... Help you out.
帮... 帮助你
Whatever you need.
不论你需要什么
Alicia.
艾莉西亚
Who is that man, Mommy?
妈咪 那男人是谁?
(有来生吗?)
(死亡和轮回)
What?
什么?
What the hell?
搞什么?
(玛洛 我必须让一切停止 对不起)
Sophia?
苏菲亚?
I just got a message from Marlo.
我刚刚收到玛洛的简讯
Something's wrong. And her phone is off.
有事情发生了 她的电话关机
We need to find her.
我们必须找到她
Okay. Where are you?
好 你在哪里?
I'm... I'm gonna come to you.
我... 我要来找你
Marlo?
玛洛?
Marlo!
玛洛!
She's not here, man.
老兄 她不在这里
Wait. Wait!
等一下!
Marlo?
玛洛?
Forget it. She's here.
算了 她在这里
Come as fast as you can!
你尽快赶来!
I'm nearly there.
我快到了
You got to hurry.
你要快一点
Ray!
瑞!
She must be down there. Come.
她一定在下面 来吧
Okay.
好
Come on!
快点!
- Oh, my God. - No, no, no, no, no!
- 噢 我的天 - 不
Oh, my God. How long has she been under?
噢 我的天啊 她这个样子多久了?
It's been over four minutes.
已经超过四分钟了
- BVM? - Sure.
- 苏醒球? - 好
Come on. We need oxygen!
快点 我们需要氧气!
Cyrus. I'm so sorry.
塞洛斯 对不起
Forgive me.
原谅我
Will you please forgive me?
请原谅我好吗?
No pulse.
没有脉搏
Take over the compressions.
接手施加压力
Go, go, go!
快!
It's not working. Shit.
没用 该死
Stop.
停
Nothing.
没有反应
Ray.
瑞
Marlo, don't you get it?
玛洛 你不懂吗?
I need you to come back.
我需要你回来
To me.
到我身边
Marlo, Marlo...
玛洛...
Marlo? Marlo.
玛洛?
No! No!
不!
Marlo.
玛洛
You have to forgive yourself.
你必须原谅你自己
Forgive yourself, Marlo.
玛洛 原谅你自己
No!
不!
Charge 360.
充电三百六十焦耳
Okay. Okay.
好
Oh, my...
噢 我的...
It's okay. It's okay.
没关系
Hey.
嘿
Here.
这里
There you go.
来吧
Thank you.
谢谢你
You okay?
你还好吗?
Yeah.
对
I found the girl.
我找到了那个女孩
And a little boy.
还有一个小男孩
Yeah.
对
The hell with going to L.A.
管他去不去洛杉矶
I'm getting a residency right here.
我要在这里找驻院医师的工作
Be near them.
跟他们在一起
I'm gonna try.
我要去尝试
Courtney was right.
柯特妮说的没错
It's not enough to apologize.
只有道歉是不够的
We have to face up to what we've done,
我们必须面对我们所做过的事
and then forgive ourselves.
然后原谅我们自己
Some lines should not be crossed.
有一些界限是不可以跨越的
We lost a friend.
我们失去了一位朋友
We will never be the same.
我们跟以前再也不一样了
Where were you?
你在哪里?
I talked to the dean.
我跟院长谈过
How'd it go?
谈得如何?
I'm on probation.
我还在试用期
Did you bring it?
你有把它带来吗?
Here.
这里
Only Courtney knows now.
现在只有柯特妮知道
Feels so weird just being here without Courtney.
没有柯特妮一起在这里 感觉好奇怪
Anyone want to say something?
有人想要说什么吗?
Let's just get hammered.
我们来大喝一场吧
Why don't you say something?
你为什么不说点什么?
To Courtney.
敬柯特妮
(康诺家)